<HELPDOC>
<HELP KEY='bubblearea' WHEN='When on the main bubble area'>
<TEXT><![CDATA[
<html>
To <b>scroll the bubble area</b>, drag with the <em>right</em> mouse button.  Alternatively,
you can use the arrow keys while pressing the Control (Command on the Mac) key.
<a href='showme:dragarea'>Show Me</a>
<p>
To <b>resize a bubble</b>, press the <em>left</em> mouse button on the proper border and then
drag to make the bubble the desired size. <a href='showme:resizebubble'>Show Me</a>
<p>
To <b>move a bubble</b>, press the <em>right</em> mouse button and move
the bubble to its desired location.  <a href='showme:movebubble'>Show Me</a>
<p>
To <b>remove a bubble</b>, click with the <em>middle</em> mouse button on the bubble or its border.
Note that a remove bubble will replace this bubble and will slowly fade to nothingness. You can click
on this remove bubble to restore the original bubble. <a href='showme:removebubble'>Show Me</a>
<p>
To <b>search over project code</b>, click with the <em>right</em> mouse button or
use the control-O (command-O on the mac) key or the F10 key.  Using the right click will bring up the
default menu; the others will not.
<p>
To <b>search over documentation</b>, <em>control</em> click with the <em>right</em>
mouse button or use the F12 key.
<p>
To <b>search over both code and documentation</b>, <em>shift</em> click with the <em>right</em>
mouse button or use the F11 key.  This also brings up the default menu.
This can be made the default by selecting the appropriate
option.
<p>
To <b>put up the simple tool bar</b>, use F1.  The tool bar will appear in the upper left
or upper right of the display (depending on where the package explorer is located).
<p>
To <b>show the current area in context</b> use F9.  Hitting F9 again will go back to a
normal display.
<p>
To <b>change the focus bubble</b>, either move the mouse to it or use the arrow keys while
pressing ALT to move to the nearest bubble in the specified direction.
<p>
To <b>augment the programmer's log</b> either by adding a note, image, or screen dump to the current task,
or to change the current task, hit F2.

]]></TEXT>
</HELP>

<HELP KEY='bubbleborder' WHEN="When on a bubble's border">
<TEXT><![CDATA[
<html>
To <b>resize this bubble</b>, press the <em>left</em> mouse button on the proper border and then
drag to make the bubble the desired size. <a href='showme:resizebubble'>Show Me</a>
<p>
To <b>move this bubble</b>, press the <em>right</em> mouse button and move
the bubble to its desired location.  <a href='showme:movebubble'>Show Me</a>
<p>
To <b>remove this bubble</b>, click with the <em>middle</em> mouse button on the bubble or its border.
Note that a remove bubble will replace this bubble and will slowly fade to nothingness. You can click
on this remove bubble to restore the original bubble. <a href='showme:removebubble'>Show Me</a>

]]></TEXT>
</HELP>

<HELP KEY='bubblecontent' WHEN='When inside a bubble'>
<TEXT><![CDATA[
<html>
To <b>resize this bubble</b>, press the <em>left</em> mouse button on the proper border and then
drag to make the bubble the desired size.  <a href='showme:resizebubble'>Show Me</a>
<p>
To <b>move this bubble</b>, press the <em>right</em> mouse button and move the bubble to its desired location.
<a href='showme:movebubble'>Show Me</a>
<p>
To <b>remove this bubble</b>, click with the <em>middle</em> mouse button on the bubble or its border.
Alternatively, you can use <em>ESC</em> or <em>control-W</em> (command-W on the Mac).
<a href='showme:removebubble'>Show Me</a>
<p>
To <b>make this bubble the current focus</b>, move the mouse inside it and/or <em>left</em>
click on the appropriate field
that should hold the focus.
<p>
To <b>get a context menu for this bubble</b>, <em>right</em> click inside the bubble.  Note the actual context
menu might depend on where in the bubble you click since it can represent the local context.
<p>
To <b>fix this bubble's location on the display</b>, right click and choose <em>Make Fixed</em> if the
option exists.	Not all bubbles can be fixed in this way.  To undo this setting, right click and choose
<em>Make Floating</em>
<p>
To <b>link this bubble to another</b>, press the <em>control</em> key and then drag a line from the
starting bubble to the ending bubble using the <em>right</em> mouse button.  This will unlink the
bubbles if they are already linked.
]]></TEXT>
</HELP>

<HELP KEY='bubblegroup' WHEN='When on a bubble group outline'>
<TEXT><![CDATA[
<html>
To <b>move all bubble in this group</b>, press down in the group border drag
with the <em>right</em> mouse button and drag to its desired location.
<p>
To <b>remove all bubbles in this group</b>, <em>double</em> click with the <em>middle</em> mouse
button on the group area.  The remove bubble that remains will restore all bubbles in the group.
<p>
To <b>title this group</b>, <em>left</em> click on the title area at the top of the group
and type in (or edit) the group name.
<p>
To <b>merge a bubble into a group</b> just move that bubble (using right-drag) until it joins
the group.
<p>
To <b>merge two groups</b>, place the groups near each other and then move a single bubble so that it
spans the groups and makes them one.
<p>
To <b>resize a bubble</b>, press the <em>left</em> mouse button on the proper border and then
drag to make the bubble the desired size. <a href='showme:resizebubble'>Show Me</a>
<p>
To <b>remove a bubble</b>, click with the <em>middle</em> mouse button on the bubble or its border.
Note that a remove bubble will replace this bubble and will slowly fade to nothingness. You can click
on this remove bubble to restore the original bubble. <a href='showme:removebubble'>Show Me</a>
]]></TEXT>
</HELP>

<HELP KEY='bubblehalo' WHEN='When on a singleton bubble group outline'>
<TEXT><![CDATA[
<html>
To <b>move this bubble</b>, press down in the group border drag
with the <em>right</em> mouse button and drag to its desired location.	Note that this
will not merge the bubble with another group as would moving the bubble directly.
<p>
To <b>remove this bubble</b>, <em>double</em> click with the <em>middle</em> mouse
button on the group area.  The remove bubble that remains will restore this bubble.
<a href='showme:removebubble'>Show Me</a>
<p>
To <b>merge this bubble into a group</b> move that bubble (using right-drag inside the bubble,
not on the bubble halo, until it joins the group.
<p>
To <b>resize this bubble</b>, press the <em>left</em> mouse button on the proper border and then
drag to make the bubble the desired size. <a href='showme:resizebubble'>Show Me</a>
]]></TEXT>
</HELP>

<HELP KEY='bubblelink' WHEN='When on a link between bubbles'>
<TEXT><![CDATA[
<html>
To <b>remove this link</b>, either control-drag a line from the start bubble to the end bubble or
click with the <em>right</em> mouse button to get a context menu and choose <em?Remove</em>
<p>
To <b>changke the link style</b>, <em>right</em> click on the link and choose the <em>Style</em>
option you want.
<p>
To <b>collapse a linke</b>, <em>right</em> click on the link and choose the <em>Collapse</em>
option.  This will bring the target bubble close to the source bubble.
]]></TEXT>
</HELP>

<HELP KEY='overviewarea' WHEN='When in the overview bar'>
<TEXT><![CDATA[
<html>
To <b>move the viewport</b>, press the <em>right</em> mouse button in the current viewport in the
overview bar and drag it to its new location.
<p>
To <b>change the viewport</b>, click with the <em>left</em> mouse button at the desired viewport
location.  You can also press down to move the location and then drag it to its target.
<p>
To <b>move a group of bubbles</b>, press down on the bubble group with the <em>right</em> mouse
button and drag the group to the target location.  This will also work for single bubbles that
are not part of a group.  It will not move bubbles out of a group.
]]></TEXT>
</HELP>

<HELP KEY='topbar' WHEN='When in the top bar'>
<TEXT><![CDATA[
<html>
To <b>create a working set</b>, click with the <em>left</em> mouse button in the area above the current view,
where "Create Task..." is displayed.  Alternatively, use the <em>right</em> mouse button to bring up a context
menu by clicking where there is no working set and choose "Create Working Set".
<p>
To <b>clear the display</b>, use the <em>right</em> mouse button to get a context menu and then choose either
"Clear Bubbles" to remove all bubbles visible in the current viewport or "Clear All Bubbles" to remove all the
bubbles in the workspace.
<p>
To <b>load a saved working set</b>, use the <em>right</em> mouse button to get a context menu.	Then either choose
"Load Working Set" to load the working set from a file or choose a working set from the task shelf, which is the
selection to the right of the menu.
<p>
To <b>print the current display</b>, use the <em>right</em> mouse button to get a context menu and choose the "Print"
option.  Alternatively, you can choose "Export as PDF" to produce a image file for later use.

]]></TEXT>
</HELP>

<HELP KEY='topbarworkingset' WHEN='When in the top bar'>
<TEXT><![CDATA[
<html>
To <b>change the name of a working set</b>, click on the current name with the <em>left</em> mouse button and then
use keyboard editing to enter a new name.
<p>
To <b>change the size of a working set</b>, press down with the <em>left</em> mouse button near the side to change
and drag the edge to the desired size.
<p>
To <b>remove the working set</b>, use the <em>right</em> mouse button to get a context menu and then choose one of the
following:  "Remove Working Set" will remove the working set but leave all the bubbles in place; "Clear and Remove Working
Set" will remove the working set and all the bubbles it contains; "Close and Save to Task Shelf" will save the current
working set to the task shelf where it can be quickly reloaded later, close the working set and clear its bubbles.
<p>
To <b>save the working set</b>, use the <em>right</em> mouse button to get a context menu and chen choose one of the
following: "Save Working Set" to save the working set to a file; "Save Working Set To Task Shelf" to save the working
set to the task shelf where it can be quickly reloaed later; or "Close and Save to Task Shelf" which will save the
current working set to the task shelf and will clear its bubbles and remove it.
<p>
To <b>export the working set</b>, use the <em>right</em> mouse button to get a context menu and then choose one of the
following: "EMail Working Set" to send the working set in a loadable from in an e-mail message to a colleague;
"Export as PDF" to create a saved image of the working set; "EMail as PDF" to send an image of the working set; or
"Save Working Set" to save the current working set to a file.
<p?
To <b>clear the display</b>, use the <em>right</em> mouse button to get a context menu and then choose either
"Clear Bubbles in Working Set" to remove all bubbles in the current working set or "Clear All Bubbles" to remove all the
bubbles in the workspace.
<p>
To <b>load a saved working set</b>, use the <em>right</em> mouse button to get a context menu.	Then either choose
"Load Working Set" to load the working set from a file or choose a working set from the task shelf, which is the
selection to the right of the menu.
<p>
To <b>print the current display</b>, use the <em>right</em> mouse button to get a context menu and choose the "Print"
option.  Alternatively, you can choose "Export as PDF" to produce a image file for later use.

]]></TEXT>
</HELP>



</HELPDOC>







































